Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel.
Friends, Ashish, in this video
we will talk about
how to submit the declaration form of ICC Bank.
Friends, actually when you
come to know that you are going to get a job,
or you get a call from this bank
that you have
not submitted the declaration form, then the method of submitting it is
very good, so how to
submit it, we will learn step by step
in this video. So friends, let's move ahead
and before moving ahead, I
request you that if you have
not subscribed to our channel, then subscribe and
also press the bell icon so
that you can get all the upcoming banking job
notifications. A
page like this will open in front of you.
Now enter your username and
password here, then log in.
After logging in, it will open like this.
If you have not already logged in, then it is
necessary to sign up. After that,
friends, the declaration
form is visible below you, click on it,
then you will see the pre-
improvement declaration here. Here, the declaration is
mentioned in front of you.  You
must read this once, after reading it, friends, complete it,
then you will see here that you have been given
an option, now in ISM,
you click here, okay, if
you have already submitted your PAN card, then it is
fine, if you have not done so, then you will have to
submit your PAN card here, so I have already
submitted it in the boxes,
after that, friends, here is the
full address with pin code, so here
you will have to write the full address, so I am just
entering the pin code number, I have
submitted it, so here is your full
address, which is the communication address, which is the
present address, okay, then
enter the same here after giving permission, then enter your
WhatsApp number here, then
correct it here,
after that you will see that some
declaration is written here, so
after reading everything here, mark it no, if I do not have any connection
with anyone, then I will mark everything no,
actually it is written here
whether you have any blood relatives
in ICC Bank or not, do you have
any  Do you have any criminal cases or not? Have you
given any interview in ICC Bank within the last one year or not?
Okay, then
you can check all this and mention it. Okay,
if you mention it in practice, then it can get rejected. So
whatever is in your case, yes or
no, then you should check it out and
mention no here.
After doing this,
read the country which is shown here.
After doing this, the name will be added here, the
mobile number will be added, then if today is 30th November, it will be added
here, then click on I accept.
Okay, then it will be something like this.
Thank you friends, to watch such videos,
please subscribe to the channel.